import { Queries } from '@/models/api'

const MOCK_QUERIES: Queries = [
  {
    id: 'DH600438',
    question: 'Senior behind share represent together.?',
    question_date: '2022-07-10T00:00:28',
    sql_query: 'SELECT particular FROM sometimes;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['kid', 'activity'],
      rows: [
        {
          kid: 'bad',
          activity: 'minute',
        },
        {
          kid: 'test',
          activity: 'tree',
        },
        {
          kid: 'blue',
          activity: 'drop',
        },
        {
          kid: 'deep',
          activity: 'note',
        },
        {
          kid: 'serious',
          activity: 'white',
        },
        {
          kid: 'for',
          activity: 'simply',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['same'],
    nl_response: 'East let attack mention recent.',
    status: 'NOT_VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 58,
    user: {
      id: 'DH590300',
      name: 'Joseph Fischer MD',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-02-10T02:19:10',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH654243',
    question: 'Call site own officer if.?',
    question_date: '2022-07-29T23:28:45',
    sql_query: 'SELECT he, occur FROM leave;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['various', 'fact', 'more'],
      rows: [
        {
          various: 'suffer',
          fact: 'small',
          more: 'whole',
        },
        {
          various: 'claim',
          fact: 'place',
          more: 'sea',
        },
        {
          various: 'their',
          fact: 'simple',
          more: 'necessary',
        },
        {
          various: 'spend',
          fact: 'media',
          more: 'late',
        },
        {
          various: 'serious',
          fact: 'matter',
          more: 'eat',
        },
        {
          various: 'deal',
          fact: 'return',
          more: 'ago',
        },
        {
          various: 'all',
          fact: 'go',
          more: 'policy',
        },
        {
          various: 'until',
          fact: 'environment',
          more: 'sort',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['according', 'head', 'provide', 'collection', 'room'],
    nl_response: 'Car record first recent hit often far.',
    status: 'VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 100,
    user: {
      id: 'DH826063',
      name: 'Gina Snow',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-01-05T23:40:44',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH869274',
    question: 'High final garden large more order develop majority.?',
    question_date: '2020-06-12T06:43:43',
    sql_query: 'SELECT law FROM election;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['minute', 'business', 'notice', 'technology'],
      rows: [
        {
          minute: 'provide',
          business: 'well',
          notice: 'small',
          technology: 'our',
        },
        {
          minute: 'collection',
          business: 'black',
          notice: 'statement',
          technology: 'us',
        },
        {
          minute: 'do',
          business: 'those',
          notice: 'study',
          technology: 'affect',
        },
        {
          minute: 'friend',
          business: 'professional',
          notice: 'design',
          technology: 'yourself',
        },
        {
          minute: 'recognize',
          business: 'prepare',
          notice: 'deal',
          technology: 'father',
        },
        {
          minute: 'affect',
          business: 'letter',
          notice: 'author',
          technology: 'hot',
        },
        {
          minute: 'teacher',
          business: 'international',
          notice: 'good',
          technology: 'serious',
        },
        {
          minute: 'focus',
          business: 'recent',
          notice: 'rule',
          technology: 'woman',
        },
        {
          minute: 'staff',
          business: 'value',
          notice: 'value',
          technology: 'around',
        },
        {
          minute: 'we',
          business: 'kind',
          notice: 'church',
          technology: 'sea',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['board', 'world'],
    nl_response: 'Too idea the.',
    status: 'NOT_VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 9,
    user: {
      id: 'DH594898',
      name: 'John Smith',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-01-07T14:22:16',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH466948',
    question: 'Sea especially color who.?',
    question_date: '2020-08-04T23:44:16',
    sql_query: 'SELECT traditional, explain, significant, old FROM act;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['appear', 'small', 'yard', 'try', 'away'],
      rows: [
        {
          appear: 'with',
          small: 'start',
          yard: 'space',
          try: 'actually',
          away: 'mission',
        },
        {
          appear: 'inside',
          small: 'ground',
          yard: 'threat',
          try: 'particularly',
          away: 'until',
        },
        {
          appear: 'trade',
          small: 'see',
          yard: 'avoid',
          try: 'step',
          away: 'quality',
        },
        {
          appear: 'once',
          small: 'contain',
          yard: 'mouth',
          try: 'water',
          away: 'decide',
        },
        {
          appear: 'support',
          small: 'case',
          yard: 'book',
          try: 'ability',
          away: 'everybody',
        },
        {
          appear: 'while',
          small: 'whatever',
          yard: 'in',
          try: 'outside',
          away: 'green',
        },
        {
          appear: 'door',
          small: 'occur',
          yard: 'let',
          try: 'account',
          away: 'player',
        },
        {
          appear: 'hundred',
          small: 'institution',
          yard: 'free',
          try: 'once',
          away: 'serve',
        },
        {
          appear: 'mother',
          small: 'their',
          yard: 'toward',
          try: 'point',
          away: 'forget',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['security', 'room', 'trade', 'player', 'watch'],
    nl_response: 'Little know room north argue already.',
    status: 'SQL_ERROR',
    evaluation_score: 0,
    user: {
      id: 'DH183381',
      name: 'Barbara Leonard',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-04-06T16:03:47',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH515902',
    question: 'Especially next population need decision can.?',
    question_date: '2020-05-10T10:38:12',
    sql_query: 'SELECT product, church, tend, occur FROM population;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['majority', 'difficult'],
      rows: [
        {
          majority: 'wind',
          difficult: 'box',
        },
        {
          majority: 'start',
          difficult: 'word',
        },
        {
          majority: 'of',
          difficult: 'history',
        },
        {
          majority: 'address',
          difficult: 'society',
        },
        {
          majority: 'light',
          difficult: 'difference',
        },
        {
          majority: 'show',
          difficult: 'work',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['sort', 'also', 'shake'],
    nl_response: 'Rest themselves from television unit explain various.',
    status: 'SQL_ERROR',
    evaluation_score: 0,
    user: {
      id: 'DH248818',
      name: 'Johnny Hendricks',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-05-16T22:26:49',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH847002',
    question: 'Will sit today end you face deal option.?',
    question_date: '2022-02-06T08:23:14',
    sql_query: 'SELECT in, full, third FROM pretty;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['entire', 'top', 'day', 'successful', 'benefit'],
      rows: [
        {
          entire: 'not',
          top: 'among',
          day: 'plant',
          successful: 'piece',
          benefit: 'stuff',
        },
        {
          entire: 'six',
          top: 'behind',
          day: 'police',
          successful: 'them',
          benefit: 'source',
        },
        {
          entire: 'staff',
          top: 'avoid',
          day: 'soldier',
          successful: 'down',
          benefit: 'yet',
        },
        {
          entire: 'focus',
          top: 'eye',
          day: 'prepare',
          successful: 'inside',
          benefit: 'travel',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['the', 'cost', 'final', 'go', 'argue'],
    nl_response: 'Sound religious article entire.',
    status: 'SQL_ERROR',
    evaluation_score: 0,
    user: {
      id: 'DH694753',
      name: 'Nathaniel Perez',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-05-20T12:28:50',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH736568',
    question: 'Offer sound affect into decision.?',
    question_date: '2021-01-21T18:44:40',
    sql_query: 'SELECT those, ask FROM fish;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['ask', 'before', 'green', 'contain'],
      rows: [
        {
          ask: 'grow',
          before: 'age',
          green: 'break',
          contain: 'research',
        },
        {
          ask: 'including',
          before: 'bag',
          green: 'since',
          contain: 'off',
        },
        {
          ask: 'bed',
          before: 'worker',
          green: 'almost',
          contain: 'care',
        },
        {
          ask: 'marriage',
          before: 'free',
          green: 'product',
          contain: 'wrong',
        },
        {
          ask: 'have',
          before: 'true',
          green: 'citizen',
          contain: 'clearly',
        },
        {
          ask: 'prove',
          before: 'book',
          green: 'fall',
          contain: 'bring',
        },
        {
          ask: 'water',
          before: 'certain',
          green: 'section',
          contain: 'out',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['feeling'],
    nl_response: 'Forward accept buy seek admit.',
    status: 'NOT_VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 31,
    user: {
      id: 'DH741167',
      name: 'Seth Hardy',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-05-15T23:48:18',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH267397',
    question: 'Story language someone commercial impact blue own.?',
    question_date: '2021-06-12T09:22:33',
    sql_query: 'SELECT through, short, home, spring, note FROM protect;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['machine', 'work', 'artist', 'name'],
      rows: [
        {
          machine: 'almost',
          work: 'region',
          artist: 'trouble',
          name: 'PM',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['figure', 'source'],
    nl_response: 'Role water direction level.',
    status: 'SQL_ERROR',
    evaluation_score: 0,
    user: {
      id: 'DH837974',
      name: 'Clarence Hale Jr.',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-05-04T00:50:06',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH921277',
    question: 'Particular billion prove red.?',
    question_date: '2022-09-24T02:35:20',
    sql_query: 'SELECT visit FROM too;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['keep', 'option', 'senior', 'behavior'],
      rows: [
        {
          keep: 'foot',
          option: 'manager',
          senior: 'child',
          behavior: 'pass',
        },
        {
          keep: 'short',
          option: 'pick',
          senior: 'western',
          behavior: 'off',
        },
        {
          keep: 'art',
          option: 'finally',
          senior: 'spring',
          behavior: 'five',
        },
        {
          keep: 'southern',
          option: 'center',
          senior: 'maintain',
          behavior: 'hope',
        },
        {
          keep: 'realize',
          option: 'property',
          senior: 'do',
          behavior: 'discussion',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['wide'],
    nl_response: 'About nor blue shake.',
    status: 'SQL_ERROR',
    evaluation_score: 0,
    user: {
      id: 'DH758892',
      name: 'Adam Parsons',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-01-20T11:12:55',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH402159',
    question: 'Price the order head.?',
    question_date: '2021-06-29T17:07:54',
    sql_query: 'SELECT increase, ask, have FROM trip;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['scene'],
      rows: [
        {
          scene: 'knowledge',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['middle', 'attack', 'actually'],
    nl_response: 'People little generation pick range three.',
    status: 'NOT_VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 90,
    user: {
      id: 'DH652745',
      name: 'Walter Kim',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-03-12T09:02:17',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH129442',
    question: 'Bring although firm occur.?',
    question_date: '2021-03-29T09:48:08',
    sql_query: 'SELECT here, black, personal FROM today;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['how', 'room', 'finally', 'whatever'],
      rows: [
        {
          how: 'hair',
          room: 'girl',
          finally: 'shoulder',
          whatever: 'store',
        },
        {
          how: 'accept',
          room: 'opportunity',
          finally: 'scientist',
          whatever: 'our',
        },
        {
          how: 'minute',
          room: 'hit',
          finally: 'believe',
          whatever: 'economic',
        },
        {
          how: 'manage',
          room: 'pay',
          finally: 'common',
          whatever: 'magazine',
        },
        {
          how: 'cold',
          room: 'very',
          finally: 'wish',
          whatever: 'sense',
        },
        {
          how: 'tell',
          room: 'trade',
          finally: 'beautiful',
          whatever: 'right',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['money'],
    nl_response: 'Result price final through season member.',
    status: 'SQL_ERROR',
    evaluation_score: 0,
    user: {
      id: 'DH942457',
      name: 'Dr. Tonya Stafford DVM',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-02-25T16:23:00',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH967972',
    question: 'Always chance low Mr apply difficult turn skin.?',
    question_date: '2022-06-03T09:46:10',
    sql_query: 'SELECT lead, must FROM left;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['off', 'seek'],
      rows: [
        {
          off: 'season',
          seek: 'enough',
        },
        {
          off: 'tend',
          seek: 'cultural',
        },
        {
          off: 'notice',
          seek: 'laugh',
        },
        {
          off: 'small',
          seek: 'analysis',
        },
        {
          off: 'military',
          seek: 'then',
        },
        {
          off: 'perhaps',
          seek: 'whole',
        },
        {
          off: 'huge',
          seek: 'agree',
        },
        {
          off: 'have',
          seek: 'blue',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['population'],
    nl_response: 'At yeah bar.',
    status: 'NOT_VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 96,
    user: {
      id: 'DH883971',
      name: 'David Everett',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-05-17T23:56:24',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH482401',
    question: 'Whatever seem debate trouble.?',
    question_date: '2020-11-28T05:56:15',
    sql_query: 'SELECT necessary, campaign, town FROM save;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['left'],
      rows: [
        {
          left: 'receive',
        },
        {
          left: 'tell',
        },
        {
          left: 'season',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['direction'],
    nl_response: 'Technology above set admit wall drug investment.',
    status: 'SQL_ERROR',
    evaluation_score: 0,
    user: {
      id: 'DH364601',
      name: 'Amy Cabrera',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-06-29T12:18:43',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH447525',
    question: 'Soldier after natural huge even professional.?',
    question_date: '2021-04-15T15:28:40',
    sql_query: 'SELECT against, table FROM run;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['artist', 'world', 'third', 'writer', 'represent'],
      rows: [
        {
          artist: 'medical',
          world: 'first',
          third: 'cover',
          writer: 'expert',
          represent: 'hard',
        },
        {
          artist: 'material',
          world: 'find',
          third: 'wish',
          writer: 'yard',
          represent: 'Democrat',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['happen'],
    nl_response: 'Section vote whose reason.',
    status: 'NOT_VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 79,
    user: {
      id: 'DH840020',
      name: 'Lynn Pearson',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-07-06T01:55:37',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH943759',
    question: 'Expert avoid term foreign place shoulder require.?',
    question_date: '2022-03-19T05:01:34',
    sql_query: 'SELECT measure, explain, charge, south FROM matter;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['so'],
      rows: [
        {
          so: 'by',
        },
        {
          so: 'behind',
        },
        {
          so: 'nor',
        },
        {
          so: 'appear',
        },
        {
          so: 'western',
        },
        {
          so: 'imagine',
        },
        {
          so: 'tonight',
        },
        {
          so: 'away',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['PM', 'blue'],
    nl_response: 'Open work reach since question seek.',
    status: 'NOT_VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 16,
    user: {
      id: 'DH588462',
      name: 'Hannah Osborn',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-02-27T12:40:15',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH556779',
    question: 'Traditional save bit page.?',
    question_date: '2020-06-23T05:36:12',
    sql_query: 'SELECT wrong FROM might;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['writer', 'rate', 'beat', 'end', 'price'],
      rows: [
        {
          writer: 'expect',
          rate: 'throw',
          beat: 'kitchen',
          end: 'focus',
          price: 'game',
        },
        {
          writer: 'fear',
          rate: 'sort',
          beat: 'former',
          end: 'later',
          price: 'money',
        },
        {
          writer: 'fight',
          rate: 'forget',
          beat: 'executive',
          end: 'design',
          price: 'less',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['old', 'worry', 'high', 'film', 'director'],
    nl_response: 'Bed goal high box address cold.',
    status: 'NOT_VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 66,
    user: {
      id: 'DH273852',
      name: 'Brittany Hopkins',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-05-28T03:35:57',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH764628',
    question: 'Trip front nature certainly level share.?',
    question_date: '2022-10-30T00:36:22',
    sql_query: 'SELECT how FROM let;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['over'],
      rows: [
        {
          over: 'tree',
        },
        {
          over: 'article',
        },
        {
          over: 'of',
        },
        {
          over: 'event',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['friend'],
    nl_response: 'Range hand issue prepare many buy move leg.',
    status: 'NOT_VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 23,
    user: {
      id: 'DH876552',
      name: 'Christopher Welch',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-07-11T12:38:41',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH669595',
    question: 'Important bank fill picture.?',
    question_date: '2020-12-05T17:30:48',
    sql_query: 'SELECT wear FROM seven;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['whether', 'do'],
      rows: [
        {
          whether: 'thank',
          do: 'professional',
        },
        {
          whether: 'water',
          do: 'plan',
        },
        {
          whether: 'why',
          do: 'number',
        },
        {
          whether: 'hear',
          do: 'word',
        },
        {
          whether: 'cost',
          do: 'majority',
        },
        {
          whether: 'coach',
          do: 'yard',
        },
        {
          whether: 'together',
          do: 'watch',
        },
        {
          whether: 'plant',
          do: 'agreement',
        },
        {
          whether: 'card',
          do: 'food',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['real'],
    nl_response: 'Body certain check much mouth media organization may.',
    status: 'NOT_VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 22,
    user: {
      id: 'DH297156',
      name: 'Becky Ross',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-01-28T21:19:27',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH880121',
    question: 'Radio still back list nearly test.?',
    question_date: '2020-08-26T05:35:20',
    sql_query: 'SELECT cover, data FROM senior;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['camera', 'she', 'across', 'natural'],
      rows: [
        {
          camera: 'day',
          she: 'issue',
          across: 'recent',
          natural: 'answer',
        },
        {
          camera: 'I',
          she: 'trial',
          across: 'image',
          natural: 'else',
        },
        {
          camera: 'time',
          she: 'form',
          across: 'community',
          natural: 'knowledge',
        },
        {
          camera: 'day',
          she: 'sort',
          across: 'end',
          natural: 'unit',
        },
        {
          camera: 'cause',
          she: 'ago',
          across: 'responsibility',
          natural: 'data',
        },
        {
          camera: 'kid',
          she: 'above',
          across: 'better',
          natural: 'whether',
        },
        {
          camera: 'sell',
          she: 'none',
          across: 'according',
          natural: 'phone',
        },
        {
          camera: 'throughout',
          she: 'car',
          across: 'hope',
          natural: 'knowledge',
        },
        {
          camera: 'else',
          she: 'thus',
          across: 'paper',
          natural: 'region',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['director', 'throw', 'technology', 'about'],
    nl_response: 'Scene organization live one accept total.',
    status: 'VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 100,
    user: {
      id: 'DH928507',
      name: 'Dr. Denise Dawson',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-01-18T17:41:39',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH114206',
    question: 'Air place much today treatment probably.?',
    question_date: '2022-03-06T22:28:37',
    sql_query: 'SELECT nothing, me, inside, now, human FROM spring;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['sea', 'such', 'fight', 'player'],
      rows: [
        {
          sea: 'structure',
          such: 'group',
          fight: 'night',
          player: 'between',
        },
        {
          sea: 'add',
          such: 'necessary',
          fight: 'democratic',
          player: 'enough',
        },
        {
          sea: 'admit',
          such: 'camera',
          fight: 'enjoy',
          player: 'new',
        },
        {
          sea: 'it',
          such: 'still',
          fight: 'program',
          player: 'onto',
        },
        {
          sea: 'data',
          such: 'blood',
          fight: 'production',
          player: 'movie',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['able', 'minute', 'opportunity', 'fine', 'real'],
    nl_response: 'After shake raise red right dark difference.',
    status: 'NOT_VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 96,
    user: {
      id: 'DH330058',
      name: 'Neil Stokes',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-05-06T07:28:00',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH553796',
    question: 'Conference drug usually blood.?',
    question_date: '2023-04-12T20:27:53',
    sql_query: 'SELECT big, bed FROM modern;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['region', 'network', 'even', 'future', 'so'],
      rows: [
        {
          region: 'teacher',
          network: 'the',
          even: 'parent',
          future: 'trip',
          so: 'step',
        },
        {
          region: 'fear',
          network: 'court',
          even: 'trial',
          future: 'skill',
          so: 'debate',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['history', 'positive', 'political', 'term', 'none'],
    nl_response: 'Scene no participant.',
    status: 'NOT_VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 19,
    user: {
      id: 'DH666513',
      name: 'Ronald Holden',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-07-04T19:18:52',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH588727',
    question: 'Nor analysis chance nor run back old.?',
    question_date: '2021-01-03T03:23:37',
    sql_query: 'SELECT too, just, there FROM student;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['size', 'mother', 'keep'],
      rows: [
        {
          size: 'within',
          mother: 'important',
          keep: 'war',
        },
        {
          size: 'bit',
          mother: 'church',
          keep: 'any',
        },
        {
          size: 'amount',
          mother: 'air',
          keep: 'quality',
        },
        {
          size: 'own',
          mother: 'point',
          keep: 'be',
        },
        {
          size: 'prevent',
          mother: 'near',
          keep: 'high',
        },
        {
          size: 'common',
          mother: 'quality',
          keep: 'trouble',
        },
        {
          size: 'on',
          mother: 'time',
          keep: 'matter',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['draw', 'rich'],
    nl_response: 'Ask level green someone out.',
    status: 'NOT_VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 31,
    user: {
      id: 'DH241036',
      name: 'Lindsey Estes',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-01-31T09:55:21',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH446587',
    question: 'Clearly short management might long building.?',
    question_date: '2020-01-01T10:14:10',
    sql_query: 'SELECT expert, fly FROM form;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['kid', 'meet', 'myself', 'measure', 'range'],
      rows: [
        {
          kid: 'long',
          meet: 'benefit',
          myself: 'allow',
          measure: 'yeah',
          range: 'direction',
        },
        {
          kid: 'place',
          meet: 'attorney',
          myself: 'talk',
          measure: 'time',
          range: 'continue',
        },
        {
          kid: 'leader',
          meet: 'task',
          myself: 'culture',
          measure: 'because',
          range: 'case',
        },
        {
          kid: 'but',
          meet: 'different',
          myself: 'all',
          measure: 'indicate',
          range: 'total',
        },
        {
          kid: 'bit',
          meet: 'American',
          myself: 'music',
          measure: 'feeling',
          range: 'building',
        },
        {
          kid: 'condition',
          meet: 'economy',
          myself: 'college',
          measure: 'wind',
          range: 'history',
        },
        {
          kid: 'usually',
          meet: 'our',
          myself: 'feel',
          measure: 'wife',
          range: 'cost',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['money', 'risk', 'agreement', 'himself', 'military'],
    nl_response: 'Prepare that yard stuff life dream increase.',
    status: 'SQL_ERROR',
    evaluation_score: 0,
    user: {
      id: 'DH689525',
      name: 'Michelle Newman',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-04-13T21:38:17',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH282687',
    question: 'Partner tonight southern conference.?',
    question_date: '2023-06-03T07:22:38',
    sql_query: 'SELECT adult FROM strong;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['page', 'best', 'night'],
      rows: [
        {
          page: 'certain',
          best: 'participant',
          night: 'oil',
        },
        {
          page: 'these',
          best: 'movie',
          night: 'management',
        },
        {
          page: 'national',
          best: 'school',
          night: 'law',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['south', 'style', 'here'],
    nl_response: 'Say fact nice evidence time chance size.',
    status: 'NOT_VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 6,
    user: {
      id: 'DH911912',
      name: 'Aaron Bullock',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-01-22T11:03:45',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH376500',
    question: 'Conference production machine glass.?',
    question_date: '2020-10-07T07:46:52',
    sql_query: 'SELECT job FROM try;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['too', 'expect', 'toward', 'paper', 'believe'],
      rows: [
        {
          too: 'trial',
          expect: 'without',
          toward: 'building',
          paper: 'outside',
          believe: 'public',
        },
        {
          too: 'war',
          expect: 'garden',
          toward: 'white',
          paper: 'unit',
          believe: 'throw',
        },
        {
          too: 'reach',
          expect: 'market',
          toward: 'certain',
          paper: 'organization',
          believe: 'stop',
        },
        {
          too: 'world',
          expect: 'glass',
          toward: 'husband',
          paper: 'agency',
          believe: 'style',
        },
        {
          too: 'money',
          expect: 'arrive',
          toward: 'particular',
          paper: 'set',
          believe: 'evening',
        },
        {
          too: 'individual',
          expect: 'each',
          toward: 'fish',
          paper: 'interesting',
          believe: 'impact',
        },
        {
          too: 'forward',
          expect: 'firm',
          toward: 'per',
          paper: 'once',
          believe: 'growth',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['let', 'both', 'speak'],
    nl_response: 'Represent oil past father before teach act.',
    status: 'VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 100,
    user: {
      id: 'DH422459',
      name: 'Michael Price',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-01-03T07:16:21',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH312135',
    question: 'Rise go direction truth tend water where.?',
    question_date: '2021-03-26T06:44:01',
    sql_query: 'SELECT deal, can, politics FROM have;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['air', 'however', 'recent', 'he'],
      rows: [
        {
          air: 'course',
          however: 'resource',
          recent: 'physical',
          he: 'once',
        },
        {
          air: 'he',
          however: 'article',
          recent: 'off',
          he: 'account',
        },
        {
          air: 'politics',
          however: 'face',
          recent: 'eye',
          he: 'detail',
        },
        {
          air: 'too',
          however: 'total',
          recent: 'yard',
          he: 'sport',
        },
        {
          air: 'cover',
          however: 'blood',
          recent: 'southern',
          he: 'another',
        },
        {
          air: 'ever',
          however: 'manage',
          recent: 'future',
          he: 'offer',
        },
        {
          air: 'serious',
          however: 'such',
          recent: 'recent',
          he: 'five',
        },
        {
          air: 'play',
          however: 'time',
          recent: 'above',
          he: 'discuss',
        },
        {
          air: 'wish',
          however: 'yeah',
          recent: 'than',
          he: 'I',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['move', 'dark'],
    nl_response: 'Not weight alone either.',
    status: 'SQL_ERROR',
    evaluation_score: 0,
    user: {
      id: 'DH837012',
      name: 'Cameron Li',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-07-31T14:06:25',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH939655',
    question: 'Understand anyone capital throw break onto agent.?',
    question_date: '2020-10-14T23:59:54',
    sql_query: 'SELECT agency, look, scene FROM or;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['pretty', 'people'],
      rows: [
        {
          pretty: 'positive',
          people: 'mother',
        },
        {
          pretty: 'knowledge',
          people: 'bill',
        },
        {
          pretty: 'deep',
          people: 'collection',
        },
        {
          pretty: 'police',
          people: 'worry',
        },
        {
          pretty: 'four',
          people: 'debate',
        },
        {
          pretty: 'spring',
          people: 'certainly',
        },
        {
          pretty: 'like',
          people: 'real',
        },
        {
          pretty: 'suffer',
          people: 'those',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['produce', 'chance', 'must', 'sure'],
    nl_response: 'But them group sort may.',
    status: 'NOT_VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 92,
    user: {
      id: 'DH951164',
      name: 'Nicole Campos',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-03-27T11:18:49',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH689902',
    question: 'Who understand perhaps knowledge.?',
    question_date: '2020-06-03T09:11:47',
    sql_query: 'SELECT successful FROM population;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['or', 'throw', 'three'],
      rows: [
        {
          or: 'explain',
          throw: 'feeling',
          three: 'me',
        },
        {
          or: 'feeling',
          throw: 'form',
          three: 'standard',
        },
        {
          or: 'indeed',
          throw: 'surface',
          three: 'us',
        },
        {
          or: 'level',
          throw: 'generation',
          three: 'especially',
        },
        {
          or: 'enter',
          throw: 'stage',
          three: 'much',
        },
        {
          or: 'source',
          throw: 'successful',
          three: 'ground',
        },
        {
          or: 'thank',
          throw: 'keep',
          three: 'reach',
        },
        {
          or: 'much',
          throw: 'camera',
          three: 'fact',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['ready', 'he', 'behavior', 'often'],
    nl_response: 'Peace ago relationship majority something.',
    status: 'SQL_ERROR',
    evaluation_score: 0,
    user: {
      id: 'DH277587',
      name: 'Timothy Smith',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-01-08T00:17:12',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH316631',
    question: 'Figure analysis name.?',
    question_date: '2020-02-07T03:23:12',
    sql_query: 'SELECT hospital, image FROM imagine;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['subject', 'fast', 'south', 'report', 'not'],
      rows: [
        {
          subject: 'minute',
          fast: 'court',
          south: 'above',
          report: 'feel',
          not: 'race',
        },
        {
          subject: 'area',
          fast: 'worry',
          south: 'something',
          report: 'more',
          not: 'building',
        },
        {
          subject: 'when',
          fast: 'week',
          south: 'agree',
          report: 'support',
          not: 'activity',
        },
        {
          subject: 'subject',
          fast: 'activity',
          south: 'view',
          report: 'become',
          not: 'still',
        },
        {
          subject: 'factor',
          fast: 'across',
          south: 'civil',
          report: 'door',
          not: 'stay',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['agency', 'section', 'reach'],
    nl_response: 'Agent government strong smile mother no three.',
    status: 'VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 100,
    user: {
      id: 'DH491263',
      name: 'Victoria Rodriguez',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-05-01T01:54:12',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH378018',
    question: 'Understand live site young blue across.?',
    question_date: '2021-02-04T12:18:41',
    sql_query: 'SELECT reduce, take, collection, thought FROM and;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['eight', 'clearly', 'rock'],
      rows: [
        {
          eight: 'pass',
          clearly: 'sure',
          rock: 'nation',
        },
        {
          eight: 'total',
          clearly: 'serve',
          rock: 'value',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['rule', 'experience', 'direction'],
    nl_response: 'Region garden ability help.',
    status: 'SQL_ERROR',
    evaluation_score: 0,
    user: {
      id: 'DH859110',
      name: 'Robert Washington',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-04-10T12:29:35',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH193986',
    question: 'Follow student job action past wide dog impact.?',
    question_date: '2023-01-05T20:28:30',
    sql_query: 'SELECT director, free FROM card;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['as', 'deep'],
      rows: [
        {
          as: 'stuff',
          deep: 'data',
        },
        {
          as: 'investment',
          deep: 'blood',
        },
        {
          as: 'family',
          deep: 'network',
        },
        {
          as: 'town',
          deep: 'enjoy',
        },
        {
          as: 'meet',
          deep: 'major',
        },
        {
          as: 'senior',
          deep: 'last',
        },
        {
          as: 'dinner',
          deep: 'appear',
        },
        {
          as: 'water',
          deep: 'police',
        },
        {
          as: 'fight',
          deep: 'mind',
        },
        {
          as: 'rest',
          deep: 'fish',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['next', 'career', 'section'],
    nl_response: 'Example open manage owner.',
    status: 'SQL_ERROR',
    evaluation_score: 0,
    user: {
      id: 'DH363792',
      name: 'Melinda Schmidt',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-06-06T22:05:21',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH172337',
    question: 'Treat sound group student education.?',
    question_date: '2021-11-08T14:38:36',
    sql_query: 'SELECT economic, end, order FROM help;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['painting', 'black'],
      rows: [
        {
          painting: 'strong',
          black: 'program',
        },
        {
          painting: 'control',
          black: 'skill',
        },
        {
          painting: 'end',
          black: 'agreement',
        },
        {
          painting: 'around',
          black: 'career',
        },
        {
          painting: 'crime',
          black: 'little',
        },
        {
          painting: 'two',
          black: 'against',
        },
        {
          painting: 'quality',
          black: 'management',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['behind', 'product'],
    nl_response: 'Yeah act charge light tax certain.',
    status: 'VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 100,
    user: {
      id: 'DH428834',
      name: 'Janet Lawson',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-07-18T11:32:46',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH914512',
    question: 'Minute beat purpose theory under lose.?',
    question_date: '2021-12-24T13:18:12',
    sql_query: 'SELECT different, accept, old FROM form;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['around', 'assume', 'open'],
      rows: [
        {
          around: 'development',
          assume: 'game',
          open: 'field',
        },
        {
          around: 'deep',
          assume: 'help',
          open: 'live',
        },
        {
          around: 'per',
          assume: 'live',
          open: 'couple',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['this'],
    nl_response: 'Song ball human other.',
    status: 'SQL_ERROR',
    evaluation_score: 0,
    user: {
      id: 'DH543085',
      name: 'Bethany Howard',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-03-20T06:57:50',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH602383',
    question: 'Leave respond fast party result.?',
    question_date: '2022-06-05T15:46:01',
    sql_query: 'SELECT claim, prepare, various FROM oil;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['one', 'also', 'concern', 'past'],
      rows: [
        {
          one: 'student',
          also: 'nothing',
          concern: 'drive',
          past: 'benefit',
        },
        {
          one: 'off',
          also: 'development',
          concern: 'mission',
          past: 'customer',
        },
        {
          one: 'political',
          also: 'seven',
          concern: 'report',
          past: 'bit',
        },
        {
          one: 'him',
          also: 'without',
          concern: 'able',
          past: 'without',
        },
        {
          one: 'himself',
          also: 'catch',
          concern: 'medical',
          past: 'write',
        },
        {
          one: 'cover',
          also: 'natural',
          concern: 'media',
          past: 'kitchen',
        },
        {
          one: 'organization',
          also: 'look',
          concern: 'though',
          past: 'crime',
        },
        {
          one: 'town',
          also: 'significant',
          concern: 'buy',
          past: 'key',
        },
        {
          one: 'view',
          also: 'challenge',
          concern: 'network',
          past: 'use',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['property', 'now', 'again', 'write'],
    nl_response: 'Close through must ask decide already.',
    status: 'VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 100,
    user: {
      id: 'DH656136',
      name: 'James Johnson',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-05-13T02:05:46',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH838707',
    question: 'Security party boy idea.?',
    question_date: '2020-10-13T09:51:35',
    sql_query: 'SELECT clear FROM possible;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['natural'],
      rows: [
        {
          natural: 'TV',
        },
        {
          natural: 'call',
        },
        {
          natural: 'weight',
        },
        {
          natural: 'probably',
        },
        {
          natural: 'move',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['visit', 'surface', 'hotel', 'so', 'purpose'],
    nl_response: 'Door likely behavior instead.',
    status: 'NOT_VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 13,
    user: {
      id: 'DH149630',
      name: 'Steven Jones',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-02-15T00:38:14',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH379242',
    question: 'Wrong discussion religious culture American.?',
    question_date: '2021-03-22T16:46:19',
    sql_query: 'SELECT bill, your, television, very, away FROM region;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['everyone', 'investment', 'accept', 'population'],
      rows: [
        {
          everyone: 'shoulder',
          investment: 'use',
          accept: 'rock',
          population: 'movement',
        },
        {
          everyone: 'election',
          investment: 'visit',
          accept: 'when',
          population: 'economy',
        },
        {
          everyone: 'pass',
          investment: 'or',
          accept: 'many',
          population: 'pattern',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['be'],
    nl_response: 'Ready along law land store.',
    status: 'SQL_ERROR',
    evaluation_score: 0,
    user: {
      id: 'DH314505',
      name: 'Ashley Allen',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-03-28T15:22:12',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH238338',
    question: 'Forward worker local how go.?',
    question_date: '2022-04-12T01:06:49',
    sql_query: 'SELECT detail, item, whose, some, recognize FROM could;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['key', 'outside', 'political', 'yeah', 'yourself'],
      rows: [
        {
          key: 'late',
          outside: 'begin',
          political: 'long',
          yeah: 'approach',
          yourself: 'life',
        },
        {
          key: 'culture',
          outside: 'TV',
          political: 'new',
          yeah: 'these',
          yourself: 'want',
        },
        {
          key: 'manager',
          outside: 'their',
          political: 'Mrs',
          yeah: 'and',
          yourself: 'southern',
        },
        {
          key: 'in',
          outside: 'soon',
          political: 'on',
          yeah: 'since',
          yourself: 'oil',
        },
        {
          key: 'defense',
          outside: 'discover',
          political: 'ok',
          yeah: 'major',
          yourself: 'about',
        },
        {
          key: 'under',
          outside: 'fly',
          political: 'myself',
          yeah: 'role',
          yourself: 'alone',
        },
        {
          key: 'avoid',
          outside: 'production',
          political: 'hair',
          yeah: 'much',
          yourself: 'option',
        },
        {
          key: 'beyond',
          outside: 'it',
          political: 'teach',
          yeah: 'focus',
          yourself: 'beyond',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['style'],
    nl_response: 'Myself pick PM road theory I.',
    status: 'SQL_ERROR',
    evaluation_score: 0,
    user: {
      id: 'DH662145',
      name: 'Robert Chan',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-01-02T23:45:11',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH222480',
    question: 'Play phone girl blue right ever.?',
    question_date: '2021-03-18T10:47:23',
    sql_query: 'SELECT almost, respond, receive, lay FROM eye;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['something', 'home', 'moment', 'bad', 'short'],
      rows: [
        {
          something: 'argue',
          home: 'total',
          moment: 'blue',
          bad: 'whole',
          short: 'program',
        },
        {
          something: 'democratic',
          home: 'director',
          moment: 'area',
          bad: 'attention',
          short: 'language',
        },
        {
          something: 'region',
          home: 'step',
          moment: 'huge',
          bad: 'hour',
          short: 'hotel',
        },
        {
          something: 'meeting',
          home: 'weight',
          moment: 'whose',
          bad: 'beautiful',
          short: 'big',
        },
        {
          something: 'fly',
          home: 'successful',
          moment: 'another',
          bad: 'meeting',
          short: 'suggest',
        },
        {
          something: 'exactly',
          home: 'receive',
          moment: 'clearly',
          bad: 'away',
          short: 'keep',
        },
        {
          something: 'southern',
          home: 'pick',
          moment: 'every',
          bad: 'four',
          short: 'level',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['early'],
    nl_response: 'Hair down present see will late.',
    status: 'NOT_VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 86,
    user: {
      id: 'DH456940',
      name: 'Amy Morgan',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-03-17T16:20:46',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH510825',
    question: 'Contain financial size bring company.?',
    question_date: '2022-06-22T06:18:31',
    sql_query: 'SELECT doctor, Mr, room FROM organization;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['factor', 'third'],
      rows: [
        {
          factor: 'improve',
          third: 'would',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['number', 'recently'],
    nl_response: 'Address second politics history performance.',
    status: 'SQL_ERROR',
    evaluation_score: 0,
    user: {
      id: 'DH547791',
      name: 'Barry Gentry',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-03-03T19:17:32',
  },
  {
    id: 'DH752139',
    question: 'Face sister cause film few.?',
    question_date: '2020-07-07T09:41:16',
    sql_query: 'SELECT choice, song, most FROM who;',
    sql_query_result: {
      columns: ['family', 'exist'],
      rows: [
        {
          family: 'study',
          exist: 'firm',
        },
        {
          family: 'large',
          exist: 'painting',
        },
        {
          family: 'program',
          exist: 'everybody',
        },
        {
          family: 'can',
          exist: 'more',
        },
        {
          family: 'expect',
          exist: 'from',
        },
        {
          family: 'friend',
          exist: 'voice',
        },
        {
          family: 'sense',
          exist: 'election',
        },
      ],
    },
    ai_process: ['light', 'because', 'let', 'property', 'Mr'],
    nl_response: 'Former financial force local.',
    status: 'VERIFIED',
    evaluation_score: 100,
    user: {
      id: 'DH183469',
      name: 'Cheryl Walter',
    },
    last_updated: '2023-01-25T06:34:02',
  },
]

export default MOCK_QUERIES
